stockio.com 2019-04-06

# Web Site Privacy Policy - Stockio.com

**1\. Overview**  
Thank you for visiting stockio.com (the "Web Site") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Web Site unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Web Site.

**2\. What Type of Information We Collect**  
The server on which the Web Site is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, your web browser, your operating system, your service provider, and the pages and images requested. This general information may be used to help us better understand how our site is viewed and used. We may share some general information about our site with our business partners or the general public. For example, we may share information regarding the daily number of unique users to our site with potential corporate partners or advertising opportunities. This information does not contain any of your personal data that can be used to contact you or identify you.

**3\. Governing Law and Jurisdiction**  
This Privacy Policy constitutes a contract made under and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of British Columbia, Canada.

**4\. Information protection**  
We use the highest security standard available to protect your personally identifiable information while it is in transit to us. All data stored on our servers is protected by a secure "firewall" so that no unauthorized use or activity can take place. Although we will make every effort to safeguard your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk that thieves may find a way to thwart our security system or that transmissions over the Internet will be intercepted.

**5\. Last Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 1st, 2017. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. These changes will be posted for general public view. When you visit our website, you agree to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this website constitutes your continued agreement to these terms. If you do not agree with these terms, you should cease using our website.

**6\. Contact Information**  
Questions or comments regarding the Web Site should be sent by e-mail to info@stockio.com
